Umemiya.
We've got trouble.
Yeah, I know.
So he already knew.
Who in the world...
The number of sprouts and plots don't match!
I have one extra plot left over.
Is there anything you wanna eat?
I don't mean the plots. Shishito—
Shishito peppers!?
You have a weak gut!
You sure it's gonna be okay!?
Th-They're not on the same page.
I get it. So that's the cause
of Hiragi-san's stomachaches.
So that's... Umemiya.
That man is Umemiya-san!
Shut yer trap.
What? Why's everyone here?
Hey!
These are tomatoes.
These are green peppers,
then eggplants, cucumbers, and okra.
They're all unique and cute, aren't they?
You'll be fine.
Sheesh, he never listens to others, and once
he starts talkin' he yaps till he's satisfied.
He's really...
They're all the same. Just grass.
What? Look closer.
They're totally different!
But still...
He was like this during the broadcast, too.
He's somewhat foolish.
But...
He changes the atmosphere
so much with just his voice.
I hope I get a good crop.
What is it that draws people to him?
Um!
About what happened,
please let me explain!
This situation is just too much for him.
I saw a shoplifter in the shopping street.
I chased him, and before I knew it,
I was on Shishitoren turf.
They chased me all over,
and when I thought I was done for,
these two saved me.
I admire the people of Bofurin,
but I got carried away.
I ended up sparking a clash
against Shishitoren.
I really am sorry.
Sasaki.
How do you know my name?
Thanks, man.
You say you sparked it,
but it's a result of you trying
to save the town and its people, yeah?
Then, there's no need to apologize.
As for the rest...
Leave it to your big brothers!
So?
How did these guys save you?
Oh, um, they kicked away the guy.
Kicked away!?
Man, those guys got it hard!
I know talking to them
is not gonna do any good.
I see, you kicked them away.
I was with them, and yet, I'm so ashamed.
Hiragi, you always shoulder the blame
by yourself like that.
I'm the one who told you
to keep an eye on these two.
See? Your stomach's flaring up again.
But the one who sealed the deal
definitely was Sakura-san.
Sh-Shut up!
Don't say stuff that's uncalled for!
What? You picked a fight?
Th-Those guys claimed
to be devotees of power,
but they were beating up weaklings.
So I just said they were lame.
That's all.
And that's the whole nine yards.
I see, I see.
Well said!
Huh?
I've also been thinking
how they've gotten lame lately.
Sakura. I heard about what happened
on the main street yesterday.
And today, you saved Sasaki.
Thanks for protecting my family.
I'm happy that I've gained
a reliable younger brother.
What's this feeling where I'm burning
to the tips of my ears?
I feel so relaxed that it pisses me off.
I think I kinda understand
why they're drawn to him.
Being with him must make you feel safe.
Wait, since when are you my big brother!?
I think of everyone in this town as family.
Kaji? What is it?
Shishi... toren...
Hey, Kaji! Kaji? What's wrong?
What? Something up?
Hey there!
Hello, hello, hello!
I'm the leader of Shishitoren.
Choji Tomiyama!
Ume-chan! Be fair, come out...
and fight! Fight! Fight!
L-Leader? Why is the leader here?
Retaliation? War!?
The second-in-command
of Shishitoren, Jo Togame.
That means...
He's stronger than that other guy.
What was that just now?
Huh? Sakura-san?
Suo-san! Sugishita-san!
Even you, Sasaki-kun!
W-Wait for me!
You guys stay here.
Gimme a break!
If it's a fight, lemme go at it!
I won't say it again.
I can't...
My feet won't move forward.
That guy until a few minutes ago...
Is this guy really the same person?
Yo, Tomiyama.
Ya got somethin' good there.
That belongs to us.
Yup, I know.
You mad? You mad?
You seem happy.
He's laughing as he confronts
Umemiya in that state.
What kinda monster is he?
All right, Ume-chan.
One-on-one! One-on-one!
I mean, you guys poked us first.
That's more than enough reason, right?
One-on-one! One-on-one!
That guy is so restless.
It's true that we made the first move.
But you know, you made
quite a thrashing yourself.
You got it out of your system, yeah?
Call it even.
Huh? Oh. Yeah. I get it.
H-He's satisfied?
You should hurry on...
Sheesh. Still as hasty as ever.
Now, Ume-chan. I poked at ya!
It's your turn next!
C'mon, c'mon. Give me payback!
Why do you want to fight that badly?
Huh? Oh.
It's not that I want to fight.
I want you, Ume-chan.
Ever since I became the top,
it's gotten so boring.
But you, Ume-chan,
you're also at the top but you seem
to have fun all the time, laughing like a fool.
That's so unfair.
So I'll take Furin,
Ume-chan and all, for myself.
Th-That's ridiculous!
I see.
Tomiyama, you had it rough, huh?
Huh?
Come on now.
What absurd crap are you tellin' our boss?
Huh? Why're you all here?
You know...
the boss raiding in all alone...
That's most unsatisfactory.
Sheesh... As soon as I explained
the situation, you flew out.
I always say you need to listen
to the whole story...
Hey, Othello-kun. Short time no see.
Yo, mop head.
Hey, I told you to stay over—
Shut up!
I wouldn't disrupt a one-on-one.
But I don't like it
when someone gets surrounded!
Jeez!
I'm gonna fight one-on-one now,
so everyone stand back!
Going face-to-face right here and now
might be tricky.
Look around you.
Wait, isn't this bad?
You guys better not move!
Tomiyama, I'll accept your one-on-one.
Have your guys stand back.
Okay. I'm cool as long as I fight you,
Ume-chan.
What?
Their boss is quite the softie.
Or is he just scared?
Hey. I'll crush you.
Don't get pissed cuz I hit the bulls-eye.
Hey, isn't that
one of the kids from earlier?
See, it is!
They're so dull, but I can tell!
Aren't I amazing?
You got a fierce-looking face, but you talk
like a little boy. How cute.
So pesky.
C'mon... Guys, calm down.
Hey, Choji.
Even if you want a one-on-one,
you should do it on another day.
Huh?
I mean, it's gonna get dark soon.
If you fight in the dark...
you can't get a good look
at the face you just pummeled.
Right, Othello-kun?
How are you gonna look
at your own face?
Does this mean everyone here is involved?
Then, Ume-chan, why don't we all go at it?
Huh?
Oh, I don't mean a brawl.
Each fight will be a one-on-one.
It's like an event. Doesn't that sound fun?
So like a kendo team competition.
Sounds good.
Doesn't it?
- While we're at it—
- Sounds good!
Invite them to our place—
Hurray! Hurray!
Listen to the end...
So then, the players are...
Choji and...
Umemiya.
Me and...
Othello-kun.
It's Sakura.
Let me go at the one with long hair.
Then I'll take that eyepatch.
The cutie chose me!
Hey! If it's a one-on-one,
we should be enough.
What? Isn't it more fun
if we all do it together?
For us, too.
We'd be happier this way.
You heard 'em!
Sheesh, this year's first-years...
Can I go as well?
Against Hiragi-san.
Sako. You...
Sorry, Umemiya.
Count me in, too.
BOFURIN
All right, then we have our lineup!
With our teams on the line...
Let's have a ton of fun and fight!
CAFÉ POTHOS
Should I even be here?
Of course.
Terrible, terrible, terrible,
definitely terrible.
This has got to be terrible.
You've been so noisy.
And whose fault do you think this is?
No point in making a fuss about it, Nirei.
Get something in your stomach.
It'll calm you down.
Kotoha-san, you don't get it at all.
What if... I'm saying if...
If, tomorrow, Umemiya-san
were to lose to that Choji Tomiyama,
Bofurin will be taken over by Shishitoren.
Bofurin might not exist anymore!
That said, making a fuss
won't help with anything.
It'll be fine.
They're not that weak.
You know that, don't you?
Anyway, I'm done eating,
so can I go home?
That was quick!
Oh, he didn't eat the veggies.
But Umemiya-san's group isn't here yet.
They're late.
He said wait for them
but they ain't showing up.
Of course.
It must be difficult to explain
everything to that bloodthirsty bunch.
But still...
CAFÉ POTHOS
Umemiya said we'll go out
for a meal, right? Why here?
Says the guy
who ate all his omelette rice!
This place has always been famous
as the hangout for Bofurin.
I hear everyone gathers here
before a fight.
And most of all...
Ko-to-ha!
Your hairdo is cute today as always!
Looks good on you!
Okay.
By the way, those veggie sprouts I mentioned
the other day are so big now!
I'll have some delivered here
in the summer!
I'll look forward to it.
What's up with that?
As you can see, you can say she's
a "favorite" of Umemiya-san.
Wh-What? Sh-She's his girlfriend!?
Oh, you took it that way.
No way!
Sheesh, don't be so stupid.
That's right, don't be stupid!
It's nothing frivolous like a girlfriend!
TA-DAH
She's my little sister!
That's not it either.
What's going on here?
We grew up in the same group home.
That's why Ume just
rattles off on his own.
Man. Is that it?
No, hold on a sec.
Little sister? Not big sister?
- Right.
- How old are you?
Sixteen. Same as you.
Lies! You look way too old to be 16.
You look older than 20 no matter...
Watch it! What's that all of a sudden?
That's right.
Kotoha is very mature.
Sheesh.
Sugishita, you shouldn't
suddenly throw things like that.
Umemiya absolutely adores Kotoha-chan.
So if he finds out Kotoha-chan
got into any danger...
You understand, yeah?
Y-Yeah.
Yummy!
Kotoha's omelette rice
is the best in Japan!
Shut up and eat.
Huh? Hiragi, you ain't eating?
Oh.
I was just thinking about
how Shishitoren used to be.
I've also been thinking
how they've gotten lame lately.
Those guys...
Were they different in the past?
Devotees to power.
Shishitoren was a team
that simply sought strength in fighting.
It's true that a lot of them were hotheaded,
but they weren't a bunch
that chased after middle school kids.
There was one time
we had a big clash against them.
It was a gruesome brawl, but I recall
that fight feeling good in a strange way.
But ever since Tomiyama became the leader,
grisly rumors began spreading.
Stuff like today ain't anything new.
I heard stories about how they
forcefully picked fights elsewhere, too.
Tomiyama and Togame both cared
about their team more than anyone.
They were like symbols
of their devotion to power.
So why did things end up like this?
Well, the reason lies within Tomiyama.
Reason? What kind?
I don't know the details.
We'll find out after we talk tomorrow.
Talk? We're heading over
to fight tomorrow.
No, no.
A fight is a "conversation,"
Sakura-kun.
Sometimes a fist is a language where you
learn more about your opponent than words.
But it's a language that only
we would understand.
Kotoha, more please!
It's way past the time for last orders.
All right, don't be late tomorrow!
Kotoha, I'll come by again!
U-Um, everyone!
I wasn't able to give proper thanks, so...
Thank you very much for saving me.
As for tomorrow,
I'm counting on all of you!
Yeah!
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
I'll do my best.
I-It's not like I'm fighting
for your sake...
You idiot.
All you need to say is, "Leave it to me."
Leave it to your big brothers!
L-Leave it to me.
Well done!
Sakura-san, your face is totally red.
Sh-Shut up!
A fight is a conversation.
A fist is a language.
I never even thought about it like that.
All right!
Well then, let's get going!
I've never...
fought for someone
other than myself like this.
And I don't know why, but...
I feel more confident
than usual that I ain't gonna lose.
Ume-chan!
Welcome! Come on in!
Yeah.
We're comin' in.
CLASH
Sakura-san, I had a hunch about this,
but do you hate veggies?
Wh-What? Got a problem with that?
I don't have any problems
without eating any.
But since our leader Umemiya-san
is growing veggies,
perhaps veggies
are the source of his power.
So, ya wanna say that I'm weak
because I don't eat vegetables?
No, I didn't mean it that way.
All right, step outside!